‪NEXT UP ON AVATAR BLIND DATE
‪It's Jung-yun.
‪-Hey, Jung-yun.
‪-He looks even better.
‪YOON JUNG-YUN
‪SEASON 2 SOFTIE
‪Don't you think Jung-yun
‪is the most handsome male participant
‪we've ever had?
‪If I could change my face for a day,
‪I'd change it to Jung-yun's.
‪He's looking good.
‪Jung-yun looks kind of like
‪a male lead in a soap opera.
‪We'll just watch him for now.
‪She's here.
‪Min-hong looks beautiful today.
‪A picture-perfect couple.
‪Jung-yun once said
‪that he falls for women
‪who can take the lead.
‪-Oh, hello.
‪-Hello.
‪-Nice to meet you.
‪Hello.
‪-Take a seat.
‪See? She takes the lead immediately.
‪May I ask your name?
‪My name is Yoon Jung-yun.
‪-Excuse me?
‪-Yoon Jung-yun.
‪-Oh, Yoon Jung-yun.
‪-Yes.
‪-My name is…
‪-Oh, I…
‪I already know.
‪JUNG-YUN & MIN-HONG
‪I know your name.
‪So how…
‪It got quiet all of a sudden.
‪Hold on, they're feeling awkward.
‪Let's break the ice for them.
‪Min-hong, this is Eun-ji.
‪You're on an avatar blind date.
‪Just do as I tell you from now on.
‪Ask Jung-yun if he appears in Season Two.
‪Were you in ‪Better Late Than Single 2‪?
‪Yes.
‪She's surprised
‪since he doesn't look like
‪an eternal single.
‪Do you appear in Season Two?
‪Yes, I do.
‪Feel free to say whatever.
‪-But…
‪-Yes?
‪Seeing someone I saw on TV is…
‪There's no need to look at it that way.
‪We're all the same in the end.
‪Okay, got it.
‪Do you still have memories of that time?
‪-Do I remember?
‪-Yes.
‪-Do you remember clearly?
‪-Of course.
‪I still see clips on social media.
‪It's like seeing my future.
‪I see. But it might not happen like that.
‪I think Min-hong is interested.
‪I agree. She's intrigued.
‪-She's being a little blunt,
‪-Yeah.
‪but she doesn't mean it.
‪Has it been a while
‪since your last blind date?
‪After the show,
‪someone set me up on a blind date.
‪Just that one time.
‪Okay.
‪And this is my second one.
‪-Your second one?
‪-Yes.
‪I still feel nervous all the same.
‪Right, going on blind dates
‪always comes with a bit of pressure.
‪Right, there's pressure.
‪-Shall we clink?
‪-Sure.
‪Who was your Cupid?
‪Can you guess?
‪Garden… I mean, Car, the garden?
‪No, it was Seo In-guk.
‪-Oh, it was Seo In-guk?
‪-Yes.
‪That's amazing.
‪He's such a gentleman.
‪-Right.
‪-And he tries to help a lot.
‪He really does.
‪But when I met him, he looked so good.
‪It was insane.
‪You're insanely good-looking too.
‪-Me?
‪-Yes.
‪Oh, I don't…
‪I don't think so.
‪What just happened?
‪May I ask your age?
‪I was born in 2000.
‪-In 2000?
‪-Yes.
‪-Wait, a millennium baby?
‪Yeah, born in 2000.
‪I was born in 2000.
‪Yes.
‪Do I not look like it?
‪-I guess I'm older.
‪-That's right.
‪You can call me ‪nuna, ‪then.
‪Really?
‪Then that's what I'll call you.
‪Okay.
‪I hope that age-gap chemistry kicks in.
‪-Me too.
‪-Yeah.
‪Do you have a particular ideal type?
‪When it comes to my ideal type,
‪I think I like someone
‪-who I feel a good vibe from.
‪-A vibe?
‪Yes, a good vibe.
‪What kind of vibe do you get from me?
‪Oh, I think you're very pretty.
‪-Thank you.
‪-You're welcome.
‪Nice.
‪How do you think I would've done
‪in Season Two?
‪-Season Two?
‪-Yes.
‪Would you have been interested in me?
‪I think I would've picked you as someone
‪to go on a date with, yes.
‪Thank you. Same here.
‪Thank you.
‪You two should go out.
‪Let's speak casually now.
‪-I have a question.
‪-Yes?
‪Do you know how to speak casually?
‪-Is it okay to drop honorifics?
‪-Oh, I see.
‪It's okay,
‪but it's a little hard for me
‪to do it right away.
‪-It's hard?
‪-Yes.
‪If it's my first time
‪meeting someone, yes.
‪How about casual-formal?
‪Casual-formal?
‪Shall we give it a try?
‪Yes.
‪How do you feel
‪about dating someone older than you?
‪Please go ahead.
‪How do you feel
‪about dating someone older than you?
‪I've never dated
‪someone older than me before,
‪so I'm not sure yet.
‪You're not sure?
‪Then what about in the future?
‪In the future?
‪I'd need to have some experience
‪before I know for sure.
‪Excuse me.
‪Jung-yun, can we check your mic?
‪Sure.
‪Eun-ji…
‪MIN-HONG IS LEFT ALONE FOR A MOMENT
‪Why are you drinking so much water?
‪Ask her if he's handsome.
‪Min-hong, do you think
‪Jung-yun is handsome?
‪Yes, he's handsome.
‪Is he not your type?
‪He's handsome.
‪My left ear?
‪Yes, angle it so that it goes in your ear.
‪-Here?
‪-Yes, the left side.
‪JUNG-YUN IS PUTTING IN HIS EARPIECE
‪Jung-yun, can you hear me?
‪Yes, I can.
‪-You can hear him?
‪-Yes.
‪Jung-yun, this is Car, the garden.
‪You're on an avatar blind date.
‪Just do as I tell you, okay?
‪-You've got this.
‪-I hear him.
‪-You can go back now.
‪-I can?
‪Okay.
‪I'm sorry for making you wait.
‪-It's okay. Take your time.
‪-Thank you.
‪Nuna.
‪Say, ‪"Nuna."
‪He can't do it.
‪Just say it.
‪Say, ‪"Nuna."
‪-Nuna.
‪-Yes?
‪-Instead of ‪nuna‪…
‪So…
‪Instead of ‪nuna‪…
‪-Instead of ‪nuna‪…
‪-I lost my train of thought.
‪I feel so comfortable around you, ‪nuna‪.
‪So instead of ‪nuna‪…
‪-So instead of ‪nuna,
‪-Can I call you Mom?
‪Can I call you Mom?
‪Are you kidding me?
‪I'm just repeating
‪-this voice is saying.
‪-Oh, I get it.
‪"This voice."
‪Do I really seem like a mom to you?
‪-Oh…
‪-Yeah.
‪Yeah.
‪Just ignore all that
‪and tell me how you really feel.
‪Of course, you don't seem like a mom.
‪You seem like an aunt.
‪You don't seem like a mom.
‪Aunt.
‪Hold on.
‪You seem like an aunt.
‪You remind me of my aunt
‪who lives near Sangdong Lake Park.
‪This is too rude.
‪You have to choose, then.
‪Either call her aunt or beatbox.
‪Just call her aunt.
‪You're threatening him.
‪Jung-yun.
‪Raise your arm if you can hear me.
‪Do you not hear me?
‪Jung-yun, can you not hear me?
‪Why are you stopping them
‪from having a normal blind date?
‪I've never met anyone so resistant.
‪Give another command to Jung-yun.
‪Nuna‪, you're really pretty.
‪I know.
‪You're pretty handsome yourself.
‪Thanks.
‪Why didn't anyone select you?
‪Why didn't anyone select you
‪in Season One?
‪That's my biggest question too.
‪Maybe it was because you weren't there.
‪I think it's because you weren't there.
‪Oh, really?
‪Would it have been different
‪if I'd been there?
‪I think we would've had fun,
‪going on dates.
‪Are you willing
‪to get in touch with me after this?
‪Oh my gosh!
‪Well, are you willing to message me?
‪Of course, I am.
‪-You are?
‪-Yeah.
‪If you're interested, then I'm willing.
‪What does that mean?
‪You want to keep in touch or not?
‪It means we should keep in touch.
‪I'm sorry.
‪It's okay.
‪This is good.
‪I actually like younger guys.
‪I see.
‪So I feel pretty good right now.
‪I honestly like guys younger than me.
‪Oh, she's for real.
‪So…
‪Seriously…
‪-You don't have a girlfriend?
‪-What?
‪You don't have a girlfriend?
‪Of course not.
‪Car, she asked him if he has a girlfriend!
‪Are you really going to
‪give me your number after this?
‪My number? Of course, I will.
‪Can I have yours too?
‪-Yeah, of course.
‪-Really?
‪I don't have my phone on me right now,
‪-but later…
‪-Later?
‪Where?
‪Just come to the front.
‪-Okay.
‪-I'll wait for you.
‪Okay.
‪I'LL WAIT FOR YOU
‪"I'll wait for you."
‪Bye. See you later.
‪Okay, see you later. Bye.
‪What in the world? This is good.
‪-Not bad at all.
‪-Right.
‪This was today's biggest win.
‪She definitely gave off
‪that vibe of a woman older than me.
‪She seemed like someone
‪who would take charge.
‪She really carried the conversation,
‪and I found that nice.
‪If she's okay with it,
‪I'd like to see her again.
‪I'm giving him my number later.
‪I mean,
‪the priority is to become friends first.
‪So I'd like to meet up and talk to him.
‪I think we'll find something in common.
‪-Hey.
‪-Hi, ‪nuna‪.
‪-Your number.
‪-Phone number?
‪-Share yours.
‪-Okay.
‪You must be excited.
‪-What?
‪-You must be excited.
‪-About the show?
‪-Yeah.
‪Will you watch it?
‪Of course, I will.
‪Like you even have to ask.
‪He's not very experienced, right?
‪So I think I'll be
‪his first for everything.
‪I love it.
‪It's such a thrill.
‪THEY EVEN TOOK A PHOTO TOGETHER
‪AFTER THE BLIND DATE
‪Here's the last pair.
‪A/S BLIND DATE
‪LAST PAIR
‪He looks like
‪the world is ending, as usual.
‪He always has that look on his face.
‪Seung-hyun is the type
‪to fall in love quickly.
‪-So today…
‪-The way I see it…
‪He's going to meet Kang Ji-su today,
‪and he'll be super surprised.
‪I bet his type changed again yesterday.
‪I don't know what he did yesterday,
‪but I know that his type
‪changed yesterday.
‪It depends on
‪which Netflix show he watched.
‪-It'll change again today.
‪-Right.
‪AHN SEUNG-HYUN
‪THE OFFICIAL HOPELESS ROMANTIC (?)
‪-Oh!
‪-She's coming.
‪KANG JI-SU, SEASON 1
‪MOST POPULAR FEMALE, DANCE INSTRUCTOR
‪She's so pretty.
‪-She dyed her hair.
‪-Here she comes, looking gorgeous.
‪Seung-hyun is going to fall in love again.
‪-I know he will.
‪-Totally.
‪-She has such a vibe.
‪-She's making her appearance.
‪-Oh, hello.
‪-Hello.
‪Hello.
‪Please take a seat.
‪Nice to meet you.
‪Look at that huge smile.
‪His ears are really red.
‪He's so happy. Yeah, they ‪are‪ red.
‪May I ask your name?
‪It's Kang Ji-su.
‪-Really?
‪-What's your name?
‪My name is Ahn Seung-hyun.
‪-Ahn Seung-hyun?
‪-Yes.
‪Why? What is it?
‪I was shocked because you're so pretty.
‪-Really?
‪-Yes.
‪Thank you.
‪Did he just say she's pretty?
‪-I knew it.
‪-He said it right away.
‪You were in Season One, right?
‪Yes.
‪You look much prettier in person.
‪Really? Thank you.
‪He needs to slow down.
‪Car, you need to do something about this.
‪Just leave him be.
‪Let's just see how he does.
‪He's doing
‪what I'd order him to do anyway.
‪He's coming on too strong
‪by repeating how pretty she is.
‪BEFORE SEASON 2 LAUNCH
‪JI-SU DOESN'T KNOW SEUNG-HYUN
‪-Oh, hold on.
‪-Why?
‪I'm too flustered to talk.
‪-Really?
‪-Yes.
‪You didn't know I'd be here?
‪I didn't.
‪-It's…
‪-Right.
‪It's hot, isn't it?
‪Don't you think so?
‪-Yes, it's hotter than I expected,
‪-Right.
‪so I regret wearing long sleeves.
‪-But you made a good outfit choice.
‪-Yeah, but I have long pants on,
‪so it still feels really hot.
‪But I had to wear them to look nice.
‪You look nice.
‪Thank you. You look even nicer.
‪I hope these two work out.
‪They look pretty good together.
‪-Eun-ji, do you want to get started?
‪-Sure.
‪Ji-su, this is Eun-ji.
‪If you can hear me,
‪tuck your hair behind your ear.
‪JI-SU RECEIVES AVATAR ORDERS FIRST
‪She can hear me.
‪Ji-su, just repeat what I say.
‪Seung-hyun, do you appear in Season Two?
‪Seung-hyun, do you appear in Season Two
‪of ‪Better Late Than Single‪?
‪Yes, that's right.
‪I expected to see
‪one of the Season Two participants here,
‪but turns out I was wrong.
‪I mean… Gosh…
‪It feels like
‪-I'm looking at a celebrity.
‪-Then…
‪-Who did you like the most in Season One?
‪-Right.
‪You.
‪-What?
‪-You, of course.
‪Gosh, it's so fun to fish for compliments.
‪No, I'm serious.
‪Really? Then what's your usual ideal type?
‪Oh, my ideal type?
‪I guess…
‪someone who's cute?
‪-Someone who's cute?
‪-Yes.
‪What a shame.
‪Most people say I'm the pretty type.
‪I'm sorry.
‪-You're cute and pretty.
‪-I was kidding.
‪You're cute plus pretty.
‪-Cute plus pretty?
‪-Yes.
‪You think so?
‪He's over the moon.
‪What do you think of me, Seung-hyun?
‪How do I come across to you?
‪-You're beautiful.
‪-Oh, come on.
‪You told me I'm pretty too many times.
‪-I know, I've said it too many times.
‪-Say something else.
‪Other than "pretty."
‪Actually, well,
‪I've been on a lot of blind dates.
‪But not a lot of women
‪led the conversation like this.
‪-Really?
‪-So I just wanted to say
‪thank you for doing that.
‪It's really nice.
‪What else do you look for?
‪There must be a list of things
‪you look for in a woman.
‪I like bright and cheerful women.
‪-Bright?
‪-I feel attracted
‪when I see a cheerful woman,
‪when I think about it.
‪After you say,
‪"Oh, you like cheerful women?"
‪I want you to cackle.
‪Oh, you like cheerful women?
‪I'm sorry.
‪-I'm so sorry.
‪-Wow, you're really cheerful.
‪But he still likes it. See?
‪He likes it.
‪So then…
‪Have you dated at all after the show?
‪After the show…
‪Say, "It's a secret."
‪-It's a secret.
‪-Come on, why?
‪-So you're not dating?
‪-Hold on.
‪-A charming woman always has secrets.
‪-Right.
‪I was trying to charm you.
‪To get to know each other slowly, right?
‪Got it.
‪Seung-hyun, what makes you charming?
‪Me?
‪I'm not sure what makes me charming.
‪You don't? Well…
‪He says he doesn't know
‪what makes him charming.
‪Seung-hyun, repeat after me.
‪Don't make that face.
‪Act naturally,
‪not like you're being fed lines.
‪This is Car, the garden. Just do as I say
‪for this avatar blind date.
‪Hello, I'm a dentist.
‪Hello.
‪-I'm a dentist.
‪Want me to brush your teeth?
‪-Sorry, just a minute.
‪-What is it?
‪-Just say it.
‪-It's over for him.
‪-You have to do it.
‪-He can't.
‪Just relax and do it.
‪Excuse me, Ji-su.
‪It's understandable.
‪Can you give me Yeo-myung's number?
‪Can I get Yeo-myung's number?
‪Yeo-myung's number?
‪Maybe that's too awkward.
‪I'm sorry, but I'd have to ask
‪Yeo-myung first.
‪I'll ask Yeo-myung on my way home.
‪Really? Thank you.
‪I'll say my blind date liked her instead.
‪Wait, what?
‪Hold on.
‪Say, "Seung-hyun, you said
‪you are a dentist."
‪Then ask how your uvula looks
‪and open your mouth.
‪Come on, she's a lady.
‪Gosh, it's hot in here.
‪-She's refusing to do it.
‪-She's refusing.
‪She's totally refusing.
‪I…
‪-I had braces before.
‪-Yes?
‪How do my teeth look?
‪Oh, I mean, very…
‪They're very straight and nice.
‪He's flustered.
‪Seung-hyun's so flustered.
‪By the way, Ji-su…
‪You might want to whiten your teeth.
‪You look really nice in every way.
‪But there's just one thing
‪you could improve.
‪I think whitening your teeth would help.
‪You're right.
‪You know, most people
‪wouldn't say things like this.
‪I was just thinking
‪that if you whiten your teeth,
‪-you'll become a goddess.
‪-Enough.
‪-Okay, that's enough.
‪-I'm sorry.
‪I'm just kidding. But seriously,
‪I think you're a really good person.
‪-You laugh at my jokes, and I like that.
‪-Really?
‪I think it's an honor
‪to talk to you like this.
‪The honor is mine.
‪I enjoyed our blind date,
‪but I have to go home now.
‪Can you…
‪Can you stay a bit longer?
‪He said, "Stay a bit longer."
‪I'll see you next time.
‪Will there be a next time?
‪-A next time?
‪-Yes.
‪Well…
‪"Will there be a next time?"
‪I want you to yell
‪in the crew's direction,
‪"Send in the next woman!"
‪-I'll see you next time.
‪-Next, please!
‪There's no one after me!
‪-Yeo-myung isn't here. It's just me!
‪-Yeo-myung…
‪I'm serious. I'm the last one!
‪Goodbye. See you next time.
‪Take care.
‪I didn't want it to end.
‪My heart fluttered the most
‪when she first walked in.
‪I really thought she was a celebrity
‪right up until she came in.
‪-Oh, hello.
‪-Hello.
‪I thought it was insane.
‪He seems very soft and gentle.
‪I think he's very soft
‪and innocent.
‪The blind date wasn't successful,
‪but I wasn't offended or anything.
‪He's someone who struggles
‪to lead a conversation,
‪so I think he managed to talk
‪as much as he did
‪because it was an avatar blind date.
‪I think he was able to
‪carry on a conversation with me,
‪thanks to it being an avatar blind date.
‪Subtitle translation by:
‪Jenny Kim